http://www.burlesons-honey.com/terms-and-conditions

Honey Vs Sugar
Local Honey - What is It?
Honey Vs Sugar
Local Honey - What is It?
Terms of Use
The website (and all of the material that it contains) is owned by Burleson's Honey and is protected by intellectual property and other laws throughout the world. Nothing found on the website may be copied, reproduced, republished, distributed, sold, licensed, transferred or modified without the express written permission of Burleson's Honey. In addition, the trademarks, logos and service marks displayed on the website are the property of Burleson's Honey. If you are aware of material on the website that infringes copyright, please contact us through the Copyright Infringement Policy process, which is described below.
UNAUTHORIZED USE, COPYING, REPRODUCTION, MODIFICATION, REPUBLISHING, UPLOADING, DOWNLOADING, POSTING, TRANSMITTING, DISTRIBUTING OR DUPLICATING OR ANY OTHER MISUSE OF ANY PART OF THE WEBSITE IS PROHIBITED. Nothing contained in the Terms of Use or in the materials on the website should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel or otherwise, any license or right to use any material in any manner without the prior written consent of Burleson's Honey. In addition, use of the content or materials for any purpose not expressly permitted in the Terms of Use is prohibited. Privacy Policy Information Collection, Use and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you believe we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email. Cookies Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Copyright ©2018 Burleson's Honey Terms and Conditions Contact Us
